Kettle and Idols
Let's see what's going on.
I have a main project for Kettle and Idol
I would like to ask this title call cute
My three main elements
Oh!
We're going to ask you to introduce the three elements that make up who you are.
Yes, sir.
We'd like to get to know our three idols better.
Now, tell us about the three elements that make you Oguro-san.
Yes. Here's what makes me who I am.
Dan.
These are the three elements.
Okay. Now let's start with the first.
The first one is oshi.
The second one is dongki.
The third is omochi.
Mochi?
Omo.
I see. Then I'll start digging one by one.
Okay.
The first one, Oshi.
Let's hear it.
I love idols very much,
The reason why I started liking idols in the first place,
I really loved Momokuro-chan's Reni Takagi,
From there, I fell deeply into the swamp of idols.
She really is the person who made me who I am.
Really?
Yes, that's not an exaggeration.
That's quite an exaggeration.
No, no, no, no.
I don't think he has it in him.
I just wanted to be Renni-chan.
Really.
I think it's fine for Momokuro-chan to be Momokuro-chan.
Even though it's not so bad.
I like Reni-chan, who I adore,
I like Rene-chan too,
I also like Morning Musume。 I also like Morning Musume,
I also like Masaki Sato, who is a member of the Haro-professionals, and Iori Noguchi of Equal Love,
I also like Noguchi Iori-chan from Equal Love, and so on,
I am getting more and more fans of various idols,
I live my life with the support of these people.
I love idols,
I love idols, and I told them that it would be fun to go see them now,
Yes.
If I were to tell them, I would tell them that the current scene looks interesting.
I know it's a little bit, but Masaki Sato graduated from Morning Musume。 She just started teaching as a solo instructor,
She just started teaching solo.
I see.
And I happened to have a chance to meet her the other day,
I told her that I would continue to support her,
I told her that I would continue to support Morning Musume。 I was asked something like, "Is it OK if I'm not a Morning Musume member? I felt I had to support them,
I felt I had to support them,
I could feel that she was probably very anxious because she was on her own,
I felt I had to support her more than ever,
So I thought I should support her even more than before, and I wanted her supporters to support her as well.
I understand.
But you are very convincing.
Really?
5CM is also a player, so there is that.
That's why you like them.
Yes, I do.
You really like it.
I really like them.
I like all of them.
Do you go to a lot of live concerts?
I go to a lot of them.
I go to live concerts, scoring sessions, and autograph sessions,
You go to scoring sessions and autograph sessions.
Yes, I do.
I go as your house, and the other time I was online,
The other time it was online.
It was an online signing, and I couldn't ask anything I really wanted to ask,
I couldn't ask.
I couldn't ask,
I wanted to hear information that only I could get,
I see. That's right.
Is this the kind of project you are planning for the scoring session?
I think it's well-known what people like to eat,
So, what is the first thing you buy at a convenience store, which you don't seem to talk about at all?
Well, you know. You don't get asked that often, do you?
I was thinking of asking them to find out that kind of thing,
Did you make up your mind?
I couldn't ask any of them,
I guess I should have asked before.
I couldn't. I froze. I froze.
Freeze? What happens when it does that?Does it freeze? What happens when that happens?
I couldn't tell you any more.
But wait a minute. In front of Oguro-san,
There are a lot of people who do that, and I could tell that you have fans, too.
I understand.
That's right. That's why I always tell them that I understand how they feel.
I see.
So, Oguro-san's scoring sessions are all about empathy.
Empathy.
You think that your fans have the same DNA as I do,
That's right.
When I talk about songs, they sympathize with me a lot,
And I often feel the same way when I talk about songs, so we become like friends,
It's like we are friends. Inversely.
I see.
So, the scoring sessions and so on.
That kind of relationship.
You are making a great job of this. The first one Oguro-san is making.
Do you mean "guess"?
You mean you're pushing for it?
Please let me sing the Donki theme song, I want to sing it, I want to dance, I want to sing it.
This show is for you, Mr. Kogezaka.
Mr. Kogezaka, Mr. Tsukiitan, Mr. Naokachan, Mr. Toshi, the man with the information fungus, Mr. Kakutani.
This program is presented by Mr. Kakutani, the man who is in love with Mr. Kogezaka and Mr. Tsuki-tan.
LOVE